http://www.chartjungle.com/print/privacy-policy

Skip to content
Privacy Policy – (updated April 2009)
We respect your privacy! Any and all information collected at this site will be kept strictly confidential and will not be sold, reused, rented, loaned, or otherwise disclosed. Any information you give to Chart Jungle will be held with the utmost care, and will not be used in ways that you have not consented to. A more detailed explanation about how we safeguard your personal information is described below. If you have any questions, please don’t hesitate to let us know.
Chart Jungle has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for this Web site: Chart Jungle
Information Automatically Logged
Information used, IP address, ISP, Browser Type, and Date to gather broad demographic information like most websites on the internet. We use this information to see where are visitors originate from. It is only used for statistics information.
Advertisers
We use outside ad companies to display ads on our site to help support the costs of running the website. These ads may contain cookies from the advertising companies. Cookies received with banner ads are collected by our ad companies. These ad companies may use cookies and/or web beacons when they advertise on our site, which sends the advertisers (like Google from the Google Adsense program) information including your IP address, ISP, and browser type you use when visiting our website. In some cases it may check to see if you have flash installed to be able to display flash ads. This information is collected by the advertising companies to generally check for geotargeting purposes. For example, if you live in Los Angeles, restaurant ads in your area may show up. Or if you are used to visiting a jewelry site, shops that carry jewelry may show up in the ads.
DoubleClick DART cookies
DART cookies may also be used for ad serving through Google’s DoubleClick. This will place a cookie on your computer when you are browsing the web and visit a site using DoubleClick advertising (including some Google AdSense advertisements). Information gained from your browsing habits and interested may cause ads to be served that are targeted to your interests by this cookie. (”interest based targeting”). The ads served will be targeted based on your previous browsing history (For example, if you have been viewing sites about visiting Las Angeles, you may see Las Angeles hotel advertisements when viewing a non-related site, such as on a site about soccer). DART uses “non personally identifiable information”. It does NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, telephone number, social security numbers, bank account numbers or credit card numbers. You can opt-out of this ad serving on all sites using this advertising by visiting http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/dart_adserving.aspx
Registration Forms
Our site’s registration form requires users to give us contact information (like their name, email, and postal address).
Contact information from the registration form is used to get in touch with the person when necessary. Other contact information for updates are used only to add persons to the update emailing lists or for contacting contest winners of the update list. Contact information sent with tips/ideas is used for giving credit for the tips/crafts ideas that are sent in.
External Links
This site contains links to other sites. Chart Jungle is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. A link may take you to a non-family oriented website, if another website has been changed since Chart Jungle first linked to it. This does happen often on the internet. Sites come and go over time. If you find a link that is not directed to where we intentioned it to go, please contact us.
Customer information collected through Affiliate web sites may be shared with -outside- third parties for marketing, order fulfillment, and any other purposes.
Public Forums
This site makes chat rooms, forums, message boards, and/or news groups available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information.
Choice/Opt-Out
You can contact us to opt-out of newsletters that you have subscribed to.
Use of Cookies
We only use cookies in instances to keep adveritising from being shown too often. An example is a 30 day cookie, which will allow you to only see a certain ad once and not again for 30 days. These are placed in different areas of our site at ChartJungle.com
You can chose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security. However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites. This could include the inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into forums or accounts.
Data Quality/Access
This site gives users the following options for changing and modifying information previously provided directly through our website:
You can contact us
Contacting the Web Site
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact us.
Custom Search
Follow Chart Jungle...
STEP 1 : SIGN UPGet updates of new free printable charts, giveaways, articles & more!
Name:
Email:
Powered by AWeber Email Newsletters
We respect your email privacy
STEP 2 : GET FREE PRINTABLES!
CategoriesCategories
Select Category
Behavior  (13)
Bookmarks  (1)
Bracelets  (1)
Calendars  (3)
Activities  (3)
Car Ribbons  (1)
Cards  (1)
Checklists  (1)
Education  (2)
Math  (2)
Health  (9)
Exercise  (3)
Weight Loss  (9)
Holidays  (1)
Home  (21)
Budget  (6)
Checklist  (1)
Clothing  (3)
Finances  (1)
Goals  (6)
Inventory  (1)
Repairs  (1)
Notes  (2)
People  (6)
Jonas Brothers  (6)
Schedules  (1)
Custom Search
Follow Chart Jungle...
STEP
1 : SIGN UP
Get updates of new free printable charts, giveaways, articles
& more!
Name:
Email:
Email Marketing by AWeber
We respect your email privacy
STEP
2 : GET FREE PRINTABLES!
CategoriesCategories
Select Category
Behavior  (13)
Bookmarks  (1)
Bracelets  (1)
Calendars  (3)
Activities  (3)
Car Ribbons  (1)
Cards  (1)
Checklists  (1)
Education  (2)
Math  (2)
Health  (9)
Exercise  (3)
Weight Loss  (9)
Holidays  (1)
Home  (21)
Budget  (6)
Checklist  (1)
Clothing  (3)
Finances  (1)
Goals  (6)
Inventory  (1)
Repairs  (1)
Notes  (2)
People  (6)
Jonas Brothers  (6)
Schedules  (1)
